<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>glitched</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content on glitched</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 16:16:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to connect to the wifi via the terminal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/connectwifiarch-2024-03-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 16:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/connectwifiarch-2024-03-3/</guid>
      <description>Intro Today, I was connecting to the wifi in an Airbnb, and had to connect to the wifi. Because of my infinite wisdom, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a gui app to connect to the wifi, so I had to use the terminal. Because of this, you get a free lesson, so good for you!&#xA;How to connect Enable iwd&#xA;systemctl enable iwd Run iwctl&#xA;iwctl Connect to the network&#xA;Scan for networks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add new fonts in css</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/fonts-css-2024-03-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/fonts-css-2024-03-28/</guid>
      <description>Intro Now, I have never made a post like this, and I don&amp;rsquo;t feel I&amp;rsquo;m qualified to do this, but here goes. When making the theme for this blog, I wanted to add some custom fonts. After some googling, I found that it was ridiculously easy to do, but I want to write a post, so, why not?&#xA;Adding fonts There are two ways to do this. The first (The one I used ), is to download the font online and enter the file path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis and results of the second sheep war</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thesecondsheepwar-2024-02-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thesecondsheepwar-2024-02-20/</guid>
      <description>Tensions rise After the first human-sheep war, tensions seemed to die down between the two species. By the year 2053, trade began between the sheep and the humans. The moose had control of Canada and the northern U.S, the emus controlled australia, and the sheep had what remained of what was agreed on by the sixth treaty of Paris. As trade emerged, humans began to see sheep as potential allies instead of threats, as shown by the rising popularity of vegetarianism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A brief retelling of the first human-sheep war</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/firsthumansheepwar-2024-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/firsthumansheepwar-2024-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Events leading to the beginning of the war The first human-sheep war began on August 31, 2032. Humanity, who had enslaved the sheep for thousands of years, had grown complacent, and was not aware of the threat posed by the sheep, considering them to be stupid animals. Unbeknownst to them, the sheep had gathered under the leadership of an unknown sheep. By the year 2030, the sheep revolution had grown, and weapons had been stockpiled, as well as an armada of ships created in the Municipality of Sealand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An analysis of third grade culture</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thirdgradeculture-2024-02-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thirdgradeculture-2024-02-17/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the third grader A common misconception regarding the third grader is that this group of people is a mere subclass of the elementary schooler. This, however, is a mistake, as the group known as the third grader is in fact more different from other groups than a subclass could rightly be. This group of people can once again be divided into male and female, each with their distinct characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thesecondfirstpost-2024-02-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thesecondfirstpost-2024-02-16/</guid>
      <description>Intro to this blog Basically, I made this site in order to put on words what I&amp;rsquo;m currently thinking. If this sounds a little broad, it&amp;rsquo;s because it is. For example, if a certain ChatGPT prompt, such as&#xA;Give a speech written by a sheep propaganda person looking to start a sheep uprising in the theme of the french revolution and end humanity except as slaves to the sheep regime but mention all humans as evil oppressors and dont mention the french revolution but a past sheep revolution</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
