<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on Glitched</title>
    <link>https://glitched.tech/tags/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on Glitched</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://glitched.tech/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s make a web ui for Conway&#39;s game of life!</title>
      <link>https://glitched.tech/gameoflife2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://glitched.tech/gameoflife2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a sequel to my &lt;a href=&#34;%22https://glitched.tech/gameoflife%22&#34;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that I may as well try to make the game of life look good. If you&amp;rsquo;re following along, I would suggest going back to the first post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Goals:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a web-based UI for the Game of Life&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make the board fit screen width and length&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Allow users to make custom setups, rather than just randomly generated ones&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;pyscript&#34;&gt;Pyscript&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since we already wrote all of this in Python, it would be a shame to get rid of it. We&amp;rsquo;ll be using &lt;a href=&#34;https://pyscript.net&#34;&gt;pyscript&lt;/a&gt; to use python in our website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s make a Brainf*** interpreter</title>
      <link>https://glitched.tech/brainf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 20:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://glitched.tech/brainf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-brainf&#34;&gt;What is Brainf***?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Brainf*** is a esoteric, Turing complete programming language involving only 8 commands and two lists. Because it is Turing complete, it is theoretically possible to compute any task doable by a computer in Brainf***, though it is significantly harder to do tasks here than in say, Python or C. It was initially designed with the goal of making the smallest possible compiler, which should make it a pretty simple project to implement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s make Conway&#39;s Game of Life in Python!</title>
      <link>https://glitched.tech/gameoflife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 22:17:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://glitched.tech/gameoflife/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-conways-game-of-life&#34;&gt;What is Conway&amp;rsquo;s game of life?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conway&amp;rsquo;s Game of Life is a simulation that runs on an infinite two dimensional grid. Each square in the grid can be in one of two states, dead or alive. On each turn, the cells interact with their neighbors, following a few rules.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every living cell with less than two live neighbors dies because of underpopulation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every living cell with more than three neighbors dies because of overpopulation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
